<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Country Travel Guide</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_button">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="india_button">India</string>
    <string name="nepal_button">Nepal</string>

    <string name="bangladesh_text">

        Its a land of otherworldly landscapes for travel
        from stunning lakes and endless rolling plains to the snow-capped Himalayas in the north.
        Its also home to wild festivals, romantic mausoleums and some of the most hectic cities in the world.
        Bangladesh came into being as
        the People Republic of Bangladesh
        when Bengali East Pakistan seceded from the union with (West) Pakistan in 1971
        The country occupies an area of 143998 km² compared, it is slightly larger than Greece (131,957 km²)
        slightly smaller than the US state of Iowa.which is 150 km long.
        The Malnicherra Tea Estate, the oldest tea garden in the subcontinent.
        Ancient historical Panam City. Ilish fish and Muslin gauze like Jamdani.
        Bangladeshs tourist attractions include historical monuments,
        resorts, beaches, picnic spots, forests and tribal people, wildlife of various species.
        Activities for tourists include angling, water skiing, river
        cruising, hiking, rowing, yachting, and sea bathing

    </string>
   <string name="india_text">
       India, country that occupies the greater part of South Asia.
       Its capital is New Delhi, built in the 20th century just south of the
       historic hub of Old Delhi to serve as India administrative centre.
       Its government is a constitutional republic that represents a
       highly diverse population consisting of thousands of ethnic groups and likely hundreds of languages.
       With roughly one sixth of the worlds total population,
       India is the second most populous country, after China.
       To get a small idea of its splendor, check out our photo gallery featuring 30 spectacular scenes travelers to India will want to see.
       Admittedly we have barely even scratched the surface of the incredible country of India, but heres a selection of some of its most beautiful places.
   </string>
    <string name="nepal_text">
        Land of mystic mountains and tales, Nepal is a paradise for hikers hidden between China and India.
        Its been an important trading point for silk and it is also said that Nepal is the birth place of Buddha.
        Home of the Himalayas, its high peaks taunts many aspiring alpinists for its real challenge:
        the Mount Everest. Nepal is finally a haven of peace and tolerance.
        Nepal, country of Asia, lying along the southern slopes of the Himalayan mountain ranges.
        It is a landlocked country located between India to the east, south, and west
        and the Tibet Autonomous Region of China to the north. Its territory extends roughly
        500 miles (800 kilometres) from east to west and 90 to 150 miles from north to south. The capital is Kathmandu.


    </string>
</resources>